Guide to the Beverly Lowry Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2016-070, 7.5 Linear Feet; 7.5 boxes
  - Four Girls: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders, Annotated Manuscript Draft, "for D. Richards", pgs. 405-496 (3 of 3), September 2013 (Box 2446, Folder 7)
  - Three CDs titled "Transcripts YSM", "Disc-MS-Day 2 & Disc RS & Misc", and "Hanna 2", undated (Box 2446, Folder 8)
  - Three CDs titled "Day 1 3:00 p.m.-10:20 p.m. & Audio MS", "RS & RS transcript & Reid book & other stuff", and "Carlos' Photos, Scene, & Autopsy", undated (Box 2446, Folder 9)
  - Three CDs titled "Hanna 1", "Day 1 9:15 a.m.-3:00 p.m. MS", and "Criminal Defense Lawyers Project-Best of the Best IV-Forensics, Science & Innocence Lost", August 25, 2011 (Box 2446, Folder 10)
  - Three Notebooks for research on the case, 2011 (Box 2446, Folder 11)
  - Timeline: Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders, including notes on the case, 2011 (Box 2446, Folder 12)
  - Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders, Annotated Draft, pgs. 1-207 (1 of 2), June-September 2014 (Box 2446, Folder 13)
  - Who Killed These Girls? Austin and the Yogurt Shop Murders, Annotated Draft, pgs. 208-383 (2 of 2), June-September 2014 (Box 2446, Folder 14)
  - UHV/ABR Reading Series Posters and news articles on Lowry, 2003-2013 (Box 2446, Folder 15)
  - "YSM Jan.-July 2014"; Annotated Manuscript Draft on the suspects (Box 2446, Folder 16)
  - Photo of Lowry, Madison Bell, Pati [Criffiter], and Percival Everett, including recipe, 2013-2014 (Box 2446, Folder 17)
  - Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft (1 of 6), undated (Box 2446, Folder 18)
  - Mississippi Writers II Calendar, with Lowry for November, 1994 (Box 2446, Folder 19)
  - Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft, (2 of 6), undated (Box 2447, Folder 1)
  - Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft, (3 of 6), undated (Box 2447, Folder 2)
  - Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft, (4 of 6), undated (Box 2447, Folder 3)
  - Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft, (5 of 6), undated (Box 2447, Folder 4)
  - Yogurt Shop Murders Annotated Manuscript Draft, (6 of 6), undated (Box 2447, Folder 5)
  - Two USBs titled "YSM" (also titled "Yogurt Shop") and "Tubman & Others", undated (Box 2447, Folder 6)
  - Print out of email on photos from Lowry's office and whiteboard, undated (Box 2447, Folder 7)